Kamijou Kyousuke
Hey.
Here.
Thanks for all you've done.
You're a genius when it comes to finding rare CDs.
I'm probably just lucky is all.
This artist's performances really are incredible.
Do you want to listen too, Sayaka?
A-Are you sure?
I'd really like to have you hear it from the speakers, but we're in a hospital, so...
I'll never forget the promises we exchanged
I still see it when I close my eyes
I'll move forward as I cast off
this darkness engulfing me
How long will it be before
I see that lost future again?
I'll walk upon this Earth,
and pierce this shadowy veil of unease,
as many times as necessary
The clock that's endlessly ticked away
now tells of the beginning
Let's open the once-closed door,
with these unwavering feelings
My heart started racing once again to paint the future
Even if I get stuck in a maze,
the beautiful blue sky will always be waiting for me
So I won't be afraid
No matter what happens next, I won't give in
I'm not scared of anything anymore
Episode 3
Tiro Finale!
Man, you're so cool, Mami-san.
This isn't a magic show, you know.
Don't forget that what
we're doing is dangerous.
Yes!
It didn't drop a Grief Seed.
That's because it was just a
familiar that split off from a witch.
They don't carry Grief Seeds.
So it wasn't a witch.
We've been fighting nothing but duds lately.
We can't ignore the familiars, though.
If allowed to develop, familiars become the same kind of witch they broke off from.
Anyway, let's go.
So have you figured out
what you want to wish for?
What about you, Madoka?
Well, I guess it's hard to think of
something when you're on the spot.
Mami-san, what did you wish for?
Oh, uh... You don't really have to tell me!
In my case...
I didn't have time to think about it.
I don't really regret it.
I think my current way of life is much better than having died back there.
But you know, if you have the choice you should think it through.
I want you to have the opportunity I didn't get.
Hey, Mami-san, does your
wish have to be for yourself?
Huh?
Like hypothetically... Hypothetically, all right?
Say there was someone
who was worse off than me.
Could I use my wish for them?
You mean Kamijou-kun?
D-Didn't I say hypothetically?! Gosh!
Whoever makes the contract doesn't
necessarily need to be the target for the wish.
It's not like it hasn't happened before, either.
I can't say I like the idea, though.
If you're going to grant
a wish for someone else,
then it's vital that you know what it is you're wishing for.
Miki-san, do you want his wish to come true,
or do you want to be the person who made his wish come true?
Mami-san...
They might sound the same,
but they're completely different.
That's a harsh way of putting it.
I'm sorry, but it has to be said now.
If you went ahead without realizing that,
I'm sure you'd regret it later.
You're right.
I was being a little too naïve.
Sorry about that.
This is pretty difficult to deal with, isn't it?
You shouldn't rush your decision.
The sooner the better for me, though.
That won't do.
Girls hate guys who pressure them.
It really isn't that simple, is it?
I'm not in a position to pressure you into it.
Suggestions are against the rules too.
I guess just wishing to become a magical girl wouldn't work, huh?
Madoka, do you just thirst for power?
No, that's not what I mean...
Or maybe I do...
I mean, I'm slow, and I'm not good at anything.
So if I could be someone cool and wonderful like Mami-san,
then that in itself would be
enough to make me happy.
You could become a much more
powerful magical girl than Mami.
Huh?
The sort of wish you make
factors into it as well,
but even I can't even imagine how large a Soul Gem you might produce.
I've never met a girl with such potential before.
Come on.
You're joking, right?
No—
Madoka, are you awake?
Yeah, what's wrong?
Again?
Jeez...
W-Water...
Damn you, baldy!
If you want to drink,
drink by your damn self!
Don't make me pull that toupée off!
Thank you.
Should I make some hot chocolate?
Yeah, sure.
I wonder why Mom loves her job so much.
Working at that company
wasn't exactly her dream, was it?
Hm... it's not that she loves her job as much as she loves a challenge.
Huh?
I'm sure there are tough
and painful times for her,
but the subsequent feeling of
accomplishment is her greatest joy.
She might not have wished to work where she does now,
but she's still living her ideal way of life.
Some dreams can come true like that.
So someone's dream can be their way of life?
I'm sure opinions differ, but I
really like that about your mom.
I can respect that, and I take pride in it.
Don't you think she's wonderful too?
Yeah.
You know you're putting innocent civilians in danger, don't you?
They've been chosen by Kyubey.
They're no longer "innocent civilians."
You're leading them toward
becoming magical girls.
And I take it you don't like that?
That's right.
It's a nuisance.
Especially in the case of Kaname Madoka.
I see.
So you've noticed her potential as well.
I cannot, under any circumstances,
allow her to make a contract.
Is it because you're afraid that anyone stronger will get in your way?
Sounds like paranoia to me.
I have no reason to fight you, but...
In that case, make sure we never meet again.
I'm sure tonight's the last time we'll resolve this peacefully.
Hey, sorry for the wait.
Huh? You couldn't see Kamijou-kun?
I guess it's not a good day for him.
Seriously, I came all this way too.
It's pretty rude.
What's wrong?
There's something over there...
It's a Grief Seed!
It's about to hatch!
No way.
Why is it here?
This is bad. We've gotta get out of here!
The barrier will go up soon.
That maze thing again?
Madoka, do you know Mami-san's cell number?
No.
This isn't good...
Madoka, go and get Mami-san.
I'll watch over the seed.
You can't!
It's too dangerous!
We still have time until the witch hatches,
but you'll be stuck once the barrier goes up.
I don't know if Mami will
make it here in time...
You can't find the witch
once the maze goes up, right?
I can't let it hatch in a place like this.
Madoka, go find her.
I'll stay with Sayaka.
When Mami gets here, she'll
know my location via telepathy.
If I watch over the Grief Seed with Sayaka,
I'll be able to guide Mami to the
shortest route out of the barrier.
Thank you, Kyubey.
I'll... I'll get Mami-san here as fast as I can.
Are you scared, Sayaka?
Well, yeah.
Of course I am.
If you can come up with a wish, I can
turn you into a magical girl right here.
Operating
Theatre
Yeah.
Operating
Theatre
If things get bad enough,
I might ask you for that.
But for now, I'll wait.
This is important to me.
I'd rather not decide until I'm really ready.
Here, right?
Kyubey, what's the status?
We're good for now.
There are no signs of it hatching yet.
Sayaka-chan, are you okay?
Of course.
I'm about to fall asleep from boredom.
It's actually worse to
provoke the egg using magic.
You don't have to hurry,
so could you come as calmly as possible?
Got it.
I'm glad we made it in time.
I would've been mad at you
guys for being too reckless,
but you made the right decision this time.
Now we don't have to worry
about the witch getting—
I thought I said I didn't
want to see you again.
I'll take down the prey this time.
You two should leave.
I don't think so.
We need to get Miki-san and Kyubey.
I can guarantee their safety.
You think I'd trust you?
I-Idiot... Now's not the time for this.
I don't want to hurt you,
but I can't guarantee your
safety if you struggle too much.
This witch is nothing like the ones you've encountered so far.
Be a good girl and I'll let
you out on the way back.
Let's go, Kaname-san.
O-Okay.
Wai—
Um... Mami-san.
What is it?
I thought about my wish a lot, and...
Did you make up your mind?
Yes, but I think you might get
mad at me for being too naïve.
What's your wish?
I've never had a subject I was good at or any skill that I could be proud of.
I thought I'd spend the rest of my life without being able to help anyone,
and that I'd always be a burden.
I couldn't stand it.
But then I met you, and you showed me
what it was like to fight to save people.
You told me I might be capable of doing the same thing.
It made me happier than anything...
So my wish will be granted
if I become a magical girl.
There's nothing I wish more than to have the power to help people.
It's hard, you know.
You'll get hurt,
and you won't have time to fall in love or hang out with friends.
But I still want to become someone who never gives up, just like you.
Nobody should become someone like me.
I'm just acting cool,
but I have no one to talk
with when I'm scared or sad...
I'm forced to cry all alone.
Being a magical girl really isn't that great.
You're not alone anymore, Mami-san.
You're right.. You really are...
Will you really fight with me from now on?
Will you stay by my side?
Yes, if you're really okay
with someone like me.
Gosh...
Some role model I turned out to be.
I guess I'm really not that great after all.
Mami-san...
But since you have the chance,
you should come up with a wish.
I guess you have a point there.
It's a contract, so you might as well get something out of it.
Make yourself a billionaire,
or get yourself a wonderful boyfriend.
Anything goes!
That's not really...
How about this, then?
If you haven't thought of a wish by
the time we've taken out this witch,
how about you wish for a grand feast and a cake from Kyubey?
A-A cake?
Yeah—the largest, most extravagant party cake you've ever seen!
We'll have a party with everyone
to celebrate us joining together
as a magical girl team.
I'm going to become a
magical girl for cake?
If you don't like it, come up
with something yourself!
Mami.
Operating
Theatre
The Grief Seed has begun to move.
It's hatching.
Hurry!
Okay. Got it.
This is a special occasion,
so I'll take care of this one fast.
Hey!
I feel light.
I've never fought with such
a happy feeling before.
I'm not scared of anything anymore.
I'm no longer alone!
Sorry for the wait.
You're just in time.
Watch out.
It's coming!
Sorry to ruin the fun,
but I'm ending this now.
Here I go!
She did it!
Tiro Finale!
Don't tell me...
You two, hurry and make
a contract with me!
Madoka!
Sayaka!
Decide on your wishes!
Hurry!
That's not necessary.
I'll take care of it.
A moment later and you
would have been dead.
Burn this moment into your eyes.
This is what it means to
become a magical girl.
Give that back.
That... That... belongs to Mami-san!
I said give that back to Mami-san!
Right. These are for magical girls.
You two have no right to touch one.
One day the light of love burning in your eyes
will transcend time
and destroy one of this world's dreams
as it spirals toward the apocalypse
What is it that you seek
now that you're done hesitating?
Is there a glimpse of hope for tomorrow
beyond this greedy admiration?
I want to be armed with the power
to shatter even the darkness in my hand,
just like the ancient magic in my childhood dreams,
the next time I see your innocent smile.
In my trembling hands I hold
the courage of a plucked flower
My feelings are all I can rely on;
the prayer that awakens
the light
Illustrated by   Tsuji Santa (Nitro+)
Mami-san was really kind.
To show us what it
takes to fight, she...
Miracles and magic do exist
Episode 4
Miracles and magic do exist.